roadfly.com 2012-09-20

# Roadfly.com Privacy Policy | Roadfly.com: Car Reviews & Road Tests

Roadfly.com is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our web site. The information contained herein may change from time to time, so we advise you to periodically review this policy.

This policy will let you know:

1\. What personally identifiable information is collected from you.  
2\. What cookies are and how they are used.  
3\. How your information is used.  
4\. Who is collecting your information?  
5\. With whom your information may be shared.  
6\. How you can access, update or delete your information.  
7\. How Roadfly.com treats your personal and financial related information.  
8\. The kind of security precautions that are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information.  
9\. How Roadfly.com protects children’s privacy. and  
10\. What else you should know about your online privacy.

**What personally identifiable information does Roadfly.com collect from me?**

Roadfly.com collects information in several ways from different parts of our web site.

Some personal information is gathered when you register. During registration, Roadfly.com asks for your name and e-mail address, amongst other personal information. The more information you volunteer (and the more accurate it is), the better we are able to customize your experience. Once you register, you are no longer anonymous to Roadfly.com–you are given a Roadfly.com ID number and Username and are able to take full advantage of Roadfly.com’s many offerings.

In addition to registration, we may ask you for personal information at other times; for example when you enter a sweepstakes, contest or promotion sponsored by Roadfly.com; when you make a purchase from the Roadfly.com store; when you post a Roadfly.com classified ad.; when you submit a listing for a web site; when you make posts and comments within the forums or articles; and when you report a problem with one of our sites or services. If you contact Roadfly.com, we may keep a record of that correspondence.

* * *

**What are cookies and how does Roadfly.com use them?**

A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored by your web browser. Through the use of cookies Roadfly.com can track and store information about your use of our web site; thus allowing us to customize and tailor certain services to you. Any Roadfly.com site that requires you to log-in or a site that is customizable requires that your computer accepts cookies.

Generally, Roadfly.com uses cookies to:

(1) Remind us of who you are and to access your Roadfly.com account information (stored on our computers). Upon “Sign In”, the cookie is set and is modified upon “Sign Out”. Roadfly.com also uses cookies to store your zip code for other services, such as Yellow Pages and Classifieds.

(2) Estimate our audience size. Each browser accessing Roadfly.com is given a unique cookie, which is used to determine the extent of repeat usage by a registered user and to track advertising based on user interests and behavior.

(3) Assist Roadfly.com’s store to track visits and to process any items in your shopping basket. The information collected by cookies may also provide information to us regarding which pages you have been viewing in our store.

(4) Track entries and submissions to promotions, sweepstakes and contests. When a Roadfly.com-hosted promotion or contest uses cookies, the information written to the cookie indicates a contestant’s status through the event.

(5) Measure traffic patterns regarding Roadfly.com’s network of web sites–i.e. where you have visited and your visiting patterns in the aggregate. We use this research to understand our users’ habits so that we may improve the content, banners, and promotions that you and other users will see on our sites.

(6) Advertising networks that serve ads on Roadfly.com may also use their own cookies to to track trends in a similar matter.

Back to Top

* * *

**How does Roadfly.com use my information?**

Roadfly.com’s primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you, the user, with a customized experience on our network of sites. This experience may include such services as interactive communications and online shopping to name a few (most of these services are completely free to you). In order to provide services free of charge, we display advertisements. By knowing a little about you, Roadfly.com can deliver more relevant advertisements and content and better serve you.

Back to Top

* * *

**Who is collecting information?**

When you are on a Roadfly.com site and are asked to enter personal information, you are sharing that information with Roadfly.com alone, unless otherwise stated. If you wish for your data to remain private, you can choose not to allow data transfer by not using that particular service or area of the Roadfly.com website.

Advertisers on Roadfly.com also collect certain information. Advertisers like Google track your location on our site, what you read on our site and where in the world you are located. They use this information to serve you more relevant ads.

Back to Top

* * *

**With whom does Roadfly.com share my information?**

As a general rule, Roadfly.com will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information without your consent. Please see the Terms of Service or Use Agreements for each of our products and services for more detailed information about how your personal information may be shared. The following describes some special circumstances where your information may be disclosed.

Business Partners & Sponsors: Roadfly.com may disclose some or all of your personal information to business partners or sponsors, but notification of disclosure will be provided to you prior to data collection or prior to transfering the data. Details of shared use can be found in specific Terms of Service or Use Agreements and sweepstakes and promotions rules. Some or all data collected during a Roadfly.com promotion may be shared with the sponsor of that particular promotion. Again, notification of discloure will be provided to you prior to any transfer of data.

Many promotions offer opportunities to request additional information from sponsors By requesting more information, you give Roadfly.com permission to transfer your personal information to the sponsor so they can fulfill your request. In many instances, only your e-mail address will be shared. If more information is to be shared with the sponsor, you will be notified prior to the transfer.

Other: Roadfly.com may also disclose user information in special cases where we have reason to believe that disclosure is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interfering with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Roadfly.com’s rights or property, other Roadfly.com users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. Roadfly.com may disclose user information when we believe, in good faith, that the law requires it. Additionally, Roadfly.com may disclose user information for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain and improve our products and services.

Back to Top

* * *

**What is Roadfly.com’s policy on allowing me to update, correct or delete my personally identifiable information?**

You may edit your [Roadfly.com Account Information ](http://forum.roadfly.com/profile.php)at any time by using your Roadfly.com Username and Password. If you have forgotten your password, please [click here](http://forum.roadfly.com/login.php?do=lostpw) to request a new password. For all other problems signing in to Roadfly.com, please use the [Help Desk Forum.](http://forum.roadfly.com/forums/171-Roadfly-Help-Desk)You do not need to be logged in to post on the help desk forum.

Your Roadfly.com account can be archived or deleted, but in doing so, you will be unable to access any Members-Only area of the Roadfly.com network, including your Roadfly.com Mail account (if you have one). You may incur monetary charges when requesting to archive or delete your account, comments, posts, or other user generated content posted to and/or hosted on Roadfly.com. These fees are subject to change without notice.

To remove forum posts and/or modify information within posts Roadfly.com requires payment. Please see the [subscription settings section of your profile to access the payments page](http://forum.roadfly.com/payments.php).

If you are participating in a Roadfly.com promotion and wish to update your e-mail address on the promotion’s mailing list or wish to quit a promotion and cease receiving promotion-related e-mail, please contact [webmaster@roadfly.com](mailto:webmaster@roadfly.com).

Back to Top

* * *

**How does Roadfly.com protect my personal and financial-related information?**

In any instance where you are asked to transmit credit card information, such as during a purchase transaction from a Roadfly.com Store or for verification purposes, that information is transmitted in an encrypted format using industry-standard secure socket layer (SSL) encryption.

Back to Top

* * *

**What security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of my information?**

Your Roadfly.com Account Information is password-protected so that you are the only one who has access to your personal information. You may edit your [Roadfly.com Account Information](http://forum.roadfly.com/profile.php) by using your Roadfly.com username and password.

For security purposes, we recommend that you not divulge your password to anyone. Roadfly.com will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited e-mail. We also suggest that you sign out of your Roadfly.com account and close your browser window when you are done with your visit. This practice will ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence should you be using a computer in a shared environment.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. While every measure is taken to protect your personal information, Roadfly.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services. You transmit information at your own risk. As specified above, security protection is of utmost importance to Roadfly.com, and we put our best efforts forward to maintain security on our systems.

Back to Top

* * *

**What else should I know about my privacy?**

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online, whether it be on a message forum or through an email, that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online, it is accessible to the public, and you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Again, we suggest maintaining the secrecy of your password and exercising caution whenever you are online.

Back to Top

* * *

**Additional Information**

Questions regarding this privacy policy should be directed to [privacy@roadfly.com](mailto:privacy@roadfly.com).

**Also see…**

  * [Electronic Frontier Foundation](http://www.eff.com/) – a civil liberties organization working to protect your rights online.
  * [How to Protect Your Privacy](http://www.ftc.gov/privacy/index.html) – information from the Federal Trade Commission.

Back to Top
